

Delphine Miel

Developer - Python

- delphine.miel0318@gmail.com
 - +90 (542) 610 27 14
- Mudanya, Bursa
- https://github.com/MyBhive



ABOUT ME

I arrived at the end of my Bachelor in Python development with Openclassrooms (France).

Mother of 2 girls (6 and 8), I am actually living in Turkey for 2 years after 7 years in Germany.

I've been manager, trainer, mother and developper. I am use to deal with stressful situation to take decision. I'm now looking for job in which I'll execute with dedication and joyfulness!



EDUCATION

2020 - Present

Bachelor Developer - Python Openclassroom (France)

Nov 2016 - Dec 2016

German course B2.2 Language Institute Didactica (Esslingen, Germany)

Aug 2012 - Jul 2013

German course B1
Volkshochschule (Norderstedt, Germany)

Jun 2008

Hotel school "Cours Hotelier de Besancon" (France)

Jun 2006

High school diploma - Economics and social studies (France)



SKILLS

- Python
- Django
- SQL
- Agile Project Management
- Front-end:
 HTML CSS Bootstrap
- UML
- · Git -GitHub
- Pack Office



WORK EXPERIENCE

Advisory Board Member Oct 2017 – Oct 2018 Stuttgart - Germany

German-French Primary School
Staff recruitment- Administrator- Hygiene and security responsible (HACCP)

Sales Partner Oct 2015 – Feb 2017 France

It Works Global: Wellness Products
Team leader of 21 distribution partners
Consultant / Salesperson

Customer Consultant May 2011 – June 2012 Poitiers - France

Electricité De France SA (EDF)
Administrator of Customer data

Receptionist Sep 2010 – March 2011 Poitiers - France

Hotel Mercure Futuroscope Check in/ Check out Night Clerk Report Preparation of seminar rooms

Professional teacher and career consultant Sep 2009 – Sep 2010 Besançon - France

Cours Hotelier de Besançon Main responsible of 52 Students

Night Auditor June 2008 – April 2009 Paris CDG Airport - France

Hotel SheratonIn charge of guess safety
Night Clerk Report

LANGUAGES



French



English





German

Turkish